Hello friends
I have received certain questions from
our viewers and the first question is
what is the process for doing a motor
insurance claim and what are the
documents which is required so what you
require is the date of incident where
and which place the incident have
happened
what is the cause of the accident
if you have file in files and fr is
required in which garage you like to
place your vehicles
the driver has a valid license or not
if you are driving in heavy Vehicles you
have proper certification for driving
that heavy Vehicles
Etc all these documents are required to
process your motor claims and in a
cashless garage you get your claim done
under cash list
and if the garage is not cashless it is
reimbursement which happens in 20 to 25